

MACHINE LEARNING · CONTROL

120, Neungdong-ro, Gwangjin-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea, 05029, Republic of Korea

□ (+82) 10-2678-3302 | ☑ cowpqja3302@naver.com | 肴 jebeom.github.io | ☑ jebeom

"Experience is the best teacher."

Summary

This is Jebeom Chae who wants to become an expert in the development of control systems using machine learning or in the field of autonomous driving. And I also interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises. Through this process, I hope to grow up with my collegues.

Research Interests

Machine Learning Imitation Learning, Data-Efficient Learning **Motion Planning** Learning-based Planning, Sampling-based Planning

Education _

Konkuk University
Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN MECHANICAL AND AEROSPACE ENGINEERING

Mar. 2019 - Present

- Total GPA: 4.18/4.5
- Two years of absence due to military service

Work Experience

KIST(Korea Institute of Science and Technology

Seoul, S.Korea

STUDENT INTERN(ADVISOR: DR.KEUNWOO JANG)

Mar. 2024 - Aug. 2024

- Research on Whole-Body Control of mobile manipulator based on Model Predictive Path Integral (MPPI)
- SLAM and Navigation Using a Mobile Manipulator Platform

Yonsei University @MLCS

Seoul, S.Korea Sep. 2024 - Present

Undergraduate Student

Study on **Equivariant Neural Networks** for Data-Efficient Learning

• Conduct a weekly group study with lab Interns

Awards & Scholarship_

SCHOLARSHIP

2021-1 Academic Scholarship, for top seat last semester
 2024-1 Academic Scholarship, for top seat last semester

Seoul, S.Korea

Seoul, S.Korea

Skills____

Programming C++/C, Python, Matlab, Linux

DevOps Git, Docker, ROS2/ROS **Languages** Korean, English

Extracurricular Activity _____

ICT Mentoring Project(Probono)

Ministry of Science and ICT

MENTE

Apr. 2022 - Nov. 2022

• Gained expertise in Git skill using gitlab.

• Learned how to operate various sensors such as camera, motion sensor etc.

Korea Robot Aircraft Competition

Ministry of Trade, Industry and Energy

PARTICIPANT • Controlling the movement of the vehicle and guide the path using ROS and C/C++.

• Processing data from the vehicle to the desired format using MATLAB.

LG Aimers 4th

TRAINEE

Github Blog

Jan. 2024 - Feb. 2024

Mar. 2023 - Sep. 2023

• Taking lectures related to AI such as supervised learning, machine learning, and deep learning.

- Implement ML models utilizing Python and Scikit-learn through hackathon
- Here are some tips what I have learned through lectures and hackathon on my Tech Blog.

Notion Page Notion

WRITERS Mar. 2023 - Present

- You can check out my simple CV and the projects I have worked on so far at [this link]
- Writing specific methods of the projects and Trouble Shooting during the project

Technical Blog Jan. 2024 - Present WRITERS

- You can easily access my blog using [this link]
- Writing some posts about lecture summary, paper review, and some tips for development
- To share what I studied and to remember more longer